<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Think
Love
Share</title>
    <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Think
Love
Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thinkloveshare.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Salut, ca va ?</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/salut-ca-va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/salut-ca-va/</guid>
      <description>Salut ! Ca va ?
Ca va ! Et toi ?
Ca va !
 What a useless proloque, right? Riiight?
Well, not exaclty.
What if I told you that this quick chat is in fact useful, and probably one of the most used, daily, worldwide?
Remember of this bad boy? This is him now :)
This is this same kind of exchange used in TCP to establish a connection between a client and a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSRF to RCE with Jolokia and MBeans</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/ssrf_to_rce_with_jolokia_and_mbeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/ssrf_to_rce_with_jolokia_and_mbeans/</guid>
      <description>Okey, here&amp;rsquo;s a funny one I&amp;rsquo;ve been given to exploit recently.
The cause of this bug is simple: The lack of input sanitization
Overview of our target  A linux host (pick your favourite) A tomcat server on 127.0.0.1:8080  Basic-Auth in place Jolokia installed / deployed  A php server on 0.0.0.0:8443  Php source code analysis, the root-cause Source code wasn&amp;rsquo;t provided, but luckily, directory listing was enabled, and a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RCE on Spip and Root-Me</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/rce_on_spip_and_root_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/rce_on_spip_and_root_me/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, This article is about Spip, root-me.org, XSS, SQLi, and Remote Code Execution. Ever wondered how secure is your daily website ? Welcome. To. Php.
Quick disclaimer before we start:  In May the 23rd 2020, someone took over an admin account on root-me by password reuse and threatened to leak solutions and flags. There is no beauty in this act, no technical skill required, nor good purpose. This is just part of the &amp;ldquo;be an asshole&amp;rdquo; mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Helping Hand</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/a_helping_hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/a_helping_hand/</guid>
      <description>From time to time, I help friends to troubleshoot issues. Coding, system administration, hacking, pretty much anything as it&amp;rsquo;s a good opportunity to learn from what they are doing, and teach cool tricks at the same time. One big issue though is that I really rarely have a decent connection. Thus, using common tools such as TeamViewer, Anydesk, RDP, on anything else isn&amp;rsquo;t really working well, crashing, extra slow, &amp;hellip; So.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse XSShell</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/reverse_xsshell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/reverse_xsshell/</guid>
      <description>The initial idea While auditing a website, I found out they were using websockets to transmit data. I didn&amp;rsquo;t kow much about it so I had to ReadTheFancyManual. Once I understood that it was&amp;hellip; Well&amp;hellip; A socket one could use with web technologies, I asked myself &amp;ldquo;What do I usually do with sockets?&amp;rdquo;
Tunnels! Transfer files! Or&amp;hellip; Spawn reverse shells?!
Or&amp;hellip; Spawn a reverse XSShell??
What do we need? A websocket server import asyncio import websockets async def hello(websocket, path): print(&amp;quot;WebSocket received&amp;quot;) while True: cmd = input(&amp;quot;cmd &amp;gt; &amp;quot;) await websocket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infosec made easy</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/infosec_made_easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/infosec_made_easy/</guid>
      <description>Not translated, because I&amp;rsquo;m lazy af! :]  Original (french) here : Infosec made easy Translator here : Deepl translator   No, more seriously, having to translate (localize) and format all the articles in two languages takes a huge amount of time that completely demotivates me to write new articles, that&amp;rsquo;s why some of them are no longer translated. There will be French or English editions depending on the targeted audience, and if you ever feel like a translator&amp;hellip; Hit me up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Subpath Auditor</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/wordpress_subpath_auditor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/wordpress_subpath_auditor/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago, I had to audit a wordpress website. As it was one of my first real-life pentest, I was really hyped and ready to try extra-super-hard to compromise this target. But after a few hours, I realised that :
 Wordpress is up to date Every plugin or theme is up to date There is no custom code (At least, I found none using gobuster and big wordlists) There is no weak credentials (Same, I found none doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean there&amp;rsquo;s none.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHrc and telegram apis</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/sshrc_and_telegram_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/sshrc_and_telegram_apis/</guid>
      <description>The root cause While casually chatting with a colleague, he told me about the sshrc feature of sshd. He explained to me that he was using telegram&amp;rsquo;s API to get ssh login notifications on his phone. My first thought was &amp;ldquo;Yeah, sure, but it&amp;rsquo;s just a .rc file (custom settings), it&amp;rsquo;s usually quite easy to bypass with the right option&amp;hellip;
While saying that, I had in mind the trick with bash --noprofile --norc that can allow a new bash process to be spawned without using any configuration file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ngrok your DockerSploit</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/ngrok_your_dockersploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/ngrok_your_dockersploit/</guid>
      <description>Hey, you! Aren’t you tired of always having broken tools relying on broken software? Pissed off because you just broke your system (againnn&amp;hellip;) trying to fix your previously broken tools and now everything’s fucked-up and you want to raise penguins out of the tech world? Or even worse, you want a reverse shell but you’re :
 At your grandparents place and they lost the router password so you can’t expose ports So broke that you can’t buy nor rent a virtual private server  Well that’s oddly specific but you’re on the exact right place on earth (and on the web)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A linux caca story</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/a_linux_caca_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/a_linux_caca_story/</guid>
      <description>The root cause Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing, I was doing some cleaning in my computer&amp;rsquo;s home directory after solving some hacking challenge. To see what kind of files where still present I ran the command ta, which is aliased (in my system) to the following function.
ta () { tree -ah &amp;quot;$@&amp;quot; | lolcat; }  It lists my files recursively, showing hidden files and putting some neat rainbow colors at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 3 to 6</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_3_to_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_3_to_6/</guid>
      <description>Datadog parties A few times a month, parties are organized either at work, or in cool places nearby by the company. So far, I joined three times. Once to taste some whiskey, once to build our own terrarium and eat hand-made sushis, and once to go to a big-games bar. And every event was a huge success! :D
There are many interns, and the vibes are always chill / funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 2</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_2/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen my home? During the first week, I&amp;rsquo;ve been living with Tatiana and Mateo in a flat just below Central Park, the flat itself was really nice, but still had one problem: the building have a very strict guests policy. It was forbidden to sublease a room due to recent regulations in New-York (mainly because of RBNB&amp;rsquo;s overnight guests and&amp;hellip; MONEY of course!). Each night, going back to the building was easy, but reaching the flat was pretty challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 1</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_1/</guid>
      <description>Before I start&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ve been quite a lot (I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting that much to be honest) to ask me for news. I&amp;rsquo;d like to spend hours speaking with each of you, but the thing is that with all I have to do during the first week (register into administrative stuff, open a bank account, get well in the place, start work, socialize a bit, recover some sleep, &amp;hellip;) and the fact that I don&amp;rsquo;t have the right phone package yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThinkLoveShare&#39;s migration</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/website_migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/website_migration/</guid>
      <description>Why change ? I used to write from time to time on thinkloveshare.blogspot.com which will soon be retired, replaced by thinkloveshare.com. I decided to change for quite a few reasons, here&amp;rsquo;s the story:
 Code format  There was no easy way to display code snippets. I could have added some js beautifier / pretty printers, but I lacked time, so instead of that was just putting screenshots which is&amp;hellip; Probably the worst choice possible&amp;hellip; =]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GreHack 2018</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/grehack_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/grehack_2018/</guid>
      <description>Before I start&amp;hellip; One year ago was my first on-site hacking event : GreHack 2017 !
The conferences were great, I met a few cool people there, and the CaptureTheFlag was awesome, even tho I had almost no knowledge, there&amp;rsquo;s always a starting point huh ? I spent the whole year doing my best to gain hacking knowledge, meet people into infosec, solve challenges, join events, conferences, CTFs, &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello there !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/about/</guid>
      <description>ThinkLoveShare Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find all kind of information, mainly IT security and development related but not only. I sometime like to share random thoughts, reflections, tools, songs, writings, travels, &amp;hellip;
Whoami Resume in PDF here
Hello there ! My name is Louka Jacques-Chevallier, also known as Laluka. I love learning, teaching and sharing tips. I lived here for quite a while, and this is the place I like the most on earth, so while you&amp;rsquo;re here, enjoy the view !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Algebra</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/algebra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/algebra/</guid>
      <description>Description  Are you a real math wiz?
nc misc.chal.csaw.io 9002
 TL;DR This challenge consists in equations being thrown at us that we have to solve and send the result in order to get the flag. Python and sage, I invoke you !
Methology A friend I was talking with while solving this chall told me :
 Well, the equations are simple, let&amp;rsquo;s write a quick script to solve it !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Big boi</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/big_boi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/big_boi/</guid>
      <description>Description  Only big boi pwners will get this one!
nc pwn.chal.csaw.io 9000
 You can download the ELF here
TL;DR This challenge is a simple buffer overflow with a check that may lead to code execution. It&amp;rsquo;s an easy pwn, so one liner is the way to go !
Methology Step 1 : Use IDA to decompile the program and avoid losing time, then overflow it with the good value many time to access the &amp;ldquo;/bin/bash&amp;rdquo; statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Shell-&gt;Code</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/shell_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/shell_code/</guid>
      <description>Description  Linked lists are great! They let you chain pieces of data together.
nc pwn.chal.csaw.io 9005
 You can download the ELF file : here
TL;DR This challenge uses linked list and leaks an address, the stack is executable, a short shellcode and a relative jump will do the trick !
Methology Step 1 : Use IDA to decompile the program, find the two useful functions that fills the linked list and expose the buffer overflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Short Circuit</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/short_circuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/csaw_2018/short_circuit/</guid>
      <description>Description  Start from the monkey&amp;rsquo;s paw and work your way down the high voltage line, for every wire that is branches off has an element that is either on or off. Ignore the first bit. Standard flag format.
-Elyk
 TL;DR This challenge consists in the analysis of a lovely electronic scheme.
It is composed of diodes, wires, wires, wires and wires.
The goal is to extract bits of data from the circuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Fest - Excess ess 1</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/security_fest_2018/excess_ess_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/writeups/security_fest_2018/excess_ess_1/</guid>
      <description>This challenge is called &amp;ldquo;Excess Ess 1&amp;rdquo;, a funny name for XSS, which is an attack that consists in forcing our victim&amp;rsquo;s browser to execute code (most of the time javascript) without its consent. This challenge was proposed by the 2018&amp;rsquo;s edition of the SecurityFest CTF.
The goal Most of the time, to prove that an XSS is possible, the hacker provides a payload that pops an alert. And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what we&amp;rsquo;re asked to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 4/4 : Stack Pivot ToZeMoon !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_4of4_stak_pivot_to_ze_moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_4of4_stak_pivot_to_ze_moon/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   Pwn Road, last introductory article! I promised you some heavy stuff for the final, and what is said, is due!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 3/4 : SaperliROPette !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_3of4_saperliropette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_3of4_saperliropette/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   Pwn Road, third stop, welcome aboard! Yesterday, the simple buffer overflow and ret2libc, today, ROP, or Return Oriented Programming, and tomorrow&amp;hellip; Tomorrow the conquest of the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 2/4 : Return at libc, pick a shell !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_2of4_ret2libc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_2of4_ret2libc/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   Welcome to this 2nd article dedicated to pwning linux executables!
On the list today, the ret2libc, or return to lib C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 1/4 : Buffer Overflow, where it all began</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_1of4_buffer_overflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/hacking/pwn_1of4_buffer_overflow/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   printf(&amp;ldquo;Mr, Ms %s, bonjour. &amp;ldquo;, lecteur); Today, I want to offer you an article more sophisticated than usual, the first of new kind, an article dealing with heavy stuff, in short, an article that blows ass!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A question of standards?</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/a_question_of_standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/a_question_of_standards/</guid>
      <description>Hello dear reader,
Today, I would like to talk to you about a deep subject, but in a very superficial way. I would like to talk to you about our society, the groups that are born, live and die in it. Groups, of course, but focused on the individuals who compose them, or who oppose to them.
As usual, I will try to share with you a way of seeing things: mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Poppy Story</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/a_poppy_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/a_poppy_story/</guid>
      <description>Translation disclaimer This history was written in french, so as my english is still quite&amp;hellip; Meh. So because of the translation, most of the poetry is lost&amp;hellip; But because I can&amp;rsquo;t stand finding resources / articles available only in one language that I can&amp;rsquo;t understand, here&amp;rsquo;s the english version.
Cheers ! ;)
 How about some change ?
How about leaving the technology aside for a while, and just relax with a cup of tea ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning without headache</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/reasoning_without_headache/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/the_rest/reasoning_without_headache/</guid>
      <description>Today, I propose to take a step back on how to approach problems, research, or even&amp;hellip;. Life in general?
Prologue What I am going to tell you here is common sense to me, but it took me years to adopt these few methods, and even then, sometimes I forget to use them and quickly regret it.
I will therefore present some ideas and techniques that will serve you in your studies (cuckoo math and physics that hurts!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>