<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hacking on Think
Love
Share</title>
    <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hacking on Think
Love
Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Failed01 - DOS to RCE in jolokia</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/failed01_dos_to_rce_in_jolokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/failed01_dos_to_rce_in_jolokia/</guid>
      <description>First article of a new series! Exciting isn&amp;rsquo;t it? We often read articles or research that explain how to exploit X or how Y works. Most of the time this seems straightforward, and yet we all struggle doing our own research. We &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; that failing is &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo;, it&amp;rsquo;s part of the process, yet it can hurt or make you feel bad.
 The path I now want to take, is the wrong one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSRF to RCE with Jolokia and MBeans</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/ssrf_to_rce_with_jolokia_and_mbeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/ssrf_to_rce_with_jolokia_and_mbeans/</guid>
      <description>Okey, here&amp;rsquo;s a funny one I&amp;rsquo;ve been given to exploit recently.
The cause of this bug is simple: The lack of input sanitization
Overview of our target  A linux host (pick your favourite) A tomcat server on 127.0.0.1:8080  Basic-Auth in place Jolokia installed / deployed  A php server on 0.0.0.0:8443  Php source code analysis, the root-cause Source code wasn&amp;rsquo;t provided, but luckily, directory listing was enabled, and a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RCE on Spip and Root-Me</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/rce_on_spip_and_root_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/rce_on_spip_and_root_me/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, This article is about Spip, root-me.org, XSS, SQLi, and Remote Code Execution. Ever wondered how secure is your daily website ? Welcome. To. Php.
Quick disclaimer before we start:  In May the 23rd 2020, someone took over an admin account on root-me by password reuse and threatened to leak solutions and flags. There is no beauty in this act, no technical skill required, nor good purpose. This is just part of the &amp;ldquo;be an asshole&amp;rdquo; mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Helping Hand</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/a_helping_hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/a_helping_hand/</guid>
      <description>From time to time, I help friends to troubleshoot issues. Coding, system administration, hacking, pretty much anything as it&amp;rsquo;s a good opportunity to learn from what they are doing, and teach cool tricks at the same time. One big issue though is that I really rarely have a decent connection. Thus, using common tools such as TeamViewer, Anydesk, RDP, on anything else isn&amp;rsquo;t really working well, crashing, extra slow, &amp;hellip; So.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse XSShell</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/reverse_xsshell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/reverse_xsshell/</guid>
      <description>The initial idea While auditing a website, I found out they were using websockets to transmit data. I didn&amp;rsquo;t kow much about it so I had to ReadTheFancyManual. Once I understood that it was&amp;hellip; Well&amp;hellip; A socket one could use with web technologies, I asked myself &amp;ldquo;What do I usually do with sockets?&amp;rdquo;
Tunnels! Transfer files! Or&amp;hellip; Spawn reverse shells?!
Or&amp;hellip; Spawn a reverse XSShell??
What do we need? A websocket server import asyncio import websockets async def hello(websocket, path): print(&amp;quot;WebSocket received&amp;quot;) while True: cmd = input(&amp;quot;cmd &amp;gt; &amp;quot;) await websocket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infosec made easy</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/infosec_made_easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/infosec_made_easy/</guid>
      <description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Quand quelqu’un t’envoie un message mais qu’en fait ce message contient une petite bestiole qui se barre avec tes clés de maison, mais en profite quand même pour te piquer 20e. Après tout, pourquoi pas ?
XSSXSSXSS XSSXSSXSS XSSXSSXSS
eXternal Xml Entity (XXE) Tu vois ce qu’il y a derrière les ombres au loin ? Tu ne dois jamais y aller, c’est l’out of bound, et ca risque de voler tes haches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Subpath Auditor</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/wordpress_subpath_auditor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/wordpress_subpath_auditor/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago, I had to audit a wordpress website. As it was one of my first real-life pentest, I was really hyped and ready to try extra-super-hard to compromise this target. But after a few hours, I realised that :
 Wordpress is up to date Every plugin or theme is up to date There is no custom code (At least, I found none using gobuster and big wordlists) There is no weak credentials (Same, I found none doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean there&amp;rsquo;s none.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ngrok your DockerSploit</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/ngrok_your_dockersploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/ngrok_your_dockersploit/</guid>
      <description>Hey, you! Aren’t you tired of always having broken tools relying on broken software? Pissed off because you just broke your system (againnn&amp;hellip;) trying to fix your previously broken tools and now everything’s fucked-up and you want to raise penguins out of the tech world? Or even worse, you want a reverse shell but you’re :
 At your grandparents place and they lost the router password so you can’t expose ports So broke that you can’t buy nor rent a virtual private server  Well that’s oddly specific but you’re on the exact right place on earth (and on the web)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GreHack 2018</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/grehack_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/grehack_2018/</guid>
      <description>Before I start&amp;hellip; One year ago was my first on-site hacking event : GreHack 2017 !
The conferences were great, I met a few cool people there, and the CaptureTheFlag was awesome, even tho I had almost no knowledge, there&amp;rsquo;s always a starting point huh ? I spent the whole year doing my best to gain hacking knowledge, meet people into infosec, solve challenges, join events, conferences, CTFs, &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Algebra</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/algebra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/algebra/</guid>
      <description>Description  Are you a real math wiz?
nc misc.chal.csaw.io 9002
 TL;DR This challenge consists in equations being thrown at us that we have to solve and send the result in order to get the flag. Python and sage, I invoke you !
Methology A friend I was talking with while solving this chall told me :
 Well, the equations are simple, let&amp;rsquo;s write a quick script to solve it !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Big boi</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/big_boi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/big_boi/</guid>
      <description>Description  Only big boi pwners will get this one!
nc pwn.chal.csaw.io 9000
 You can download the ELF here
TL;DR This challenge is a simple buffer overflow with a check that may lead to code execution. It&amp;rsquo;s an easy pwn, so one liner is the way to go !
Methology Step 1 : Use IDA to decompile the program and avoid losing time, then overflow it with the good value many time to access the &amp;ldquo;/bin/bash&amp;rdquo; statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Shell-&gt;Code</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/shell_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/shell_code/</guid>
      <description>Description  Linked lists are great! They let you chain pieces of data together.
nc pwn.chal.csaw.io 9005
 You can download the ELF file : here
TL;DR This challenge uses linked list and leaks an address, the stack is executable, a short shellcode and a relative jump will do the trick !
Methology Step 1 : Use IDA to decompile the program, find the two useful functions that fills the linked list and expose the buffer overflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSAW - Short Circuit</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/short_circuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/short_circuit/</guid>
      <description>Description  Start from the monkey&amp;rsquo;s paw and work your way down the high voltage line, for every wire that is branches off has an element that is either on or off. Ignore the first bit. Standard flag format.
-Elyk
 TL;DR This challenge consists in the analysis of a lovely electronic scheme.
It is composed of diodes, wires, wires, wires and wires.
The goal is to extract bits of data from the circuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Fest - Excess ess 1</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/excess_ess_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/excess_ess_1/</guid>
      <description>This challenge is called &amp;ldquo;Excess Ess 1&amp;rdquo;, a funny name for XSS, which is an attack that consists in forcing our victim&amp;rsquo;s browser to execute code (most of the time javascript) without its consent. This challenge was proposed by the 2018&amp;rsquo;s edition of the SecurityFest CTF.
The goal Most of the time, to prove that an XSS is possible, the hacker provides a payload that pops an alert. And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what we&amp;rsquo;re asked to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 4/4 : Stack Pivot ToZeMoon !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_4of4_stak_pivot_to_ze_moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_4of4_stak_pivot_to_ze_moon/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   Pwn Road, last introductory article! I promised you some heavy stuff for the final, and what is said, is due!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 3/4 : SaperliROPette !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_3of4_saperliropette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_3of4_saperliropette/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   Pwn Road, third stop, welcome aboard! Yesterday, the simple buffer overflow and ret2libc, today, ROP, or Return Oriented Programming, and tomorrow&amp;hellip; Tomorrow the conquest of the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 2/4 : Return at libc, pick a shell !</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_2of4_ret2libc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_2of4_ret2libc/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   Welcome to this 2nd article dedicated to pwning linux executables!
On the list today, the ret2libc, or return to lib C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWN 1/4 : Buffer Overflow, where it all began</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_1of4_buffer_overflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/hacking/pwn_1of4_buffer_overflow/</guid>
      <description>Small edit after the initial publication of the articles:
These four articles lead me to give an &amp;ldquo;pwn introductory&amp;rdquo; conference at the HitchHack 2018. It summarizes the first 3 articles but goes less into detail. If this format suits you better, the slides are downloadable here and the video (French only) here :
   printf(&amp;ldquo;Mr, Ms %s, bonjour. &amp;ldquo;, lecteur); Today, I want to offer you an article more sophisticated than usual, the first of new kind, an article dealing with heavy stuff, in short, an article that blows ass!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>