<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding on Think
Love
Share</title>
    <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coding on Think
Love
Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHrc and telegram apis</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/sshrc_and_telegram_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/sshrc_and_telegram_apis/</guid>
      <description>The root cause While casually chatting with a colleague, he told me about the sshrc feature of sshd. He explained to me that he was using telegram&amp;rsquo;s API to get ssh login notifications on his phone. My first thought was &amp;ldquo;Yeah, sure, but it&amp;rsquo;s just a .rc file (custom settings), it&amp;rsquo;s usually quite easy to bypass with the right option&amp;hellip;
While saying that, I had in mind the trick with bash --noprofile --norc that can allow a new bash process to be spawned without using any configuration file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A linux caca story</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/a_linux_caca_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/a_linux_caca_story/</guid>
      <description>The root cause Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing, I was doing some cleaning in my computer&amp;rsquo;s home directory after solving some hacking challenge. To see what kind of files where still present I ran the command ta, which is aliased (in my system) to the following function.
ta () { tree -ah &amp;quot;$@&amp;quot; | lolcat; }  It lists my files recursively, showing hidden files and putting some neat rainbow colors at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThinkLoveShare&#39;s migration</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/website_migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/coding/website_migration/</guid>
      <description>Why change ? I used to write from time to time on thinkloveshare.blogspot.com which will soon be retired, replaced by thinkloveshare.com. I decided to change for quite a few reasons, here&amp;rsquo;s the story:
 Code format  There was no easy way to display code snippets. I could have added some js beautifier / pretty printers, but I lacked time, so instead of that was just putting screenshots which is&amp;hellip; Probably the worst choice possible&amp;hellip; =]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>