<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travels on Think
Love
Share</title>
    <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travels on Think
Love
Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 3 to 6</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_3_to_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_3_to_6/</guid>
      <description>Datadog parties A few times a month, parties are organized either at work, or in cool places nearby by the company. So far, I joined three times. Once to taste some whiskey, once to build our own terrarium and eat hand-made sushis, and once to go to a big-games bar. And every event was a huge success! :D
There are many interns, and the vibes are always chill / funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 2</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_2/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen my home? During the first week, I&amp;rsquo;ve been living with Tatiana and Mateo in a flat just below Central Park, the flat itself was really nice, but still had one problem: the building have a very strict guests policy. It was forbidden to sublease a room due to recent regulations in New-York (mainly because of RBNB&amp;rsquo;s overnight guests and&amp;hellip; MONEY of course!). Each night, going back to the building was easy, but reaching the flat was pretty challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 1</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/en/travels/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_1/</guid>
      <description>Before I start&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ve been quite a lot (I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting that much to be honest) to ask me for news. I&amp;rsquo;d like to spend hours speaking with each of you, but the thing is that with all I have to do during the first week (register into administrative stuff, open a bank account, get well in the place, start work, socialize a bit, recover some sleep, &amp;hellip;) and the fact that I don&amp;rsquo;t have the right phone package yet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>