<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The_rest on Think
Love
Share</title>
    <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The_rest on Think
Love
Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Salut, ca va ?</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/salut_ca_va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/salut_ca_va/</guid>
      <description>Salut ! Ca va ?
Ca va ! Et toi ?
Ca va !
 What a useless proloque, right? Riiight?
Well, not exaclty.
What if I told you that this quick chat is in fact useful, and probably one of the most used, daily, worldwide?
Remember of this bad boy? This is him now :)
This is this same kind of exchange used in TCP to establish a connection between a client and a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHrc and telegram apis</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/sshrc_and_telegram_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/sshrc_and_telegram_apis/</guid>
      <description>The root cause While casually chatting with a colleague, he told me about the sshrc feature of sshd. He explained to me that he was using telegram&amp;rsquo;s API to get ssh login notifications on his phone. My first thought was &amp;ldquo;Yeah, sure, but it&amp;rsquo;s just a .rc file (custom settings), it&amp;rsquo;s usually quite easy to bypass with the right option&amp;hellip;
While saying that, I had in mind the trick with bash --noprofile --norc that can allow a new bash process to be spawned without using any configuration file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A linux caca story</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/a_linux_caca_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/a_linux_caca_story/</guid>
      <description>The root cause Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing, I was doing some cleaning in my computer&amp;rsquo;s home directory after solving some hacking challenge. To see what kind of files where still present I ran the command ta, which is aliased (in my system) to the following function.
ta () { tree -ah &amp;quot;$@&amp;quot; | lolcat; }  It lists my files recursively, showing hidden files and putting some neat rainbow colors at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 3 to 6</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_3_to_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_3_to_6/</guid>
      <description>Datadog parties A few times a month, parties are organized either at work, or in cool places nearby by the company. So far, I joined three times. Once to taste some whiskey, once to build our own terrarium and eat hand-made sushis, and once to go to a big-games bar. And every event was a huge success! :D
There are many interns, and the vibes are always chill / funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 2</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_2/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen my home? During the first week, I&amp;rsquo;ve been living with Tatiana and Mateo in a flat just below Central Park, the flat itself was really nice, but still had one problem: the building have a very strict guests policy. It was forbidden to sublease a room due to recent regulations in New-York (mainly because of RBNB&amp;rsquo;s overnight guests and&amp;hellip; MONEY of course!). Each night, going back to the building was easy, but reaching the flat was pretty challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York, Datadog and I - Week 1</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/new_york_datadog_and_i_week_1/</guid>
      <description>Before I start&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ve been quite a lot (I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting that much to be honest) to ask me for news. I&amp;rsquo;d like to spend hours speaking with each of you, but the thing is that with all I have to do during the first week (register into administrative stuff, open a bank account, get well in the place, start work, socialize a bit, recover some sleep, &amp;hellip;) and the fact that I don&amp;rsquo;t have the right phone package yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThinkLoveShare&#39;s migration</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/website_migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/website_migration/</guid>
      <description>Why change ? I used to write from time to time on thinkloveshare.blogspot.com which will soon be retired, replaced by thinkloveshare.com. I decided to change for quite a few reasons, here&amp;rsquo;s the story:
 Code format  There was no easy way to display code snippets. I could have added some js beautifier / pretty printers, but I lacked time, so instead of that was just putting screenshots which is&amp;hellip; Probably the worst choice possible&amp;hellip; =]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A question of standards?</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/a_question_of_standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/a_question_of_standards/</guid>
      <description>Hello dear reader,
Today, I would like to talk to you about a deep subject, but in a very superficial way. I would like to talk to you about our society, the groups that are born, live and die in it. Groups, of course, but focused on the individuals who compose them, or who oppose to them.
As usual, I will try to share with you a way of seeing things: mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Une histoire de coquelicot</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/une_histoire_de_coquelicot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/une_histoire_de_coquelicot/</guid>
      <description>Et si, pour varier un peu, on prenait le large ? Et si on laissait la technologie de côté un petit instant, histoire de se divertir ? Et si on lisait un peu ?
Le concept est simple, je reçois un début de texte, d&amp;rsquo;histoire, quelques mots, une idée, et je brode dessus tant bien que mal, en espérant que le rendu final soit sympathique ! =]
Texte proposé Une femme furieuse vêtue d&amp;rsquo;une robe rouge sort du bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning without headache</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/reasoning_without_headache/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/reasoning_without_headache/</guid>
      <description>Today, I propose to take a step back on how to approach problems, research, or even&amp;hellip;. Life in general?
Prologue What I am going to tell you here is common sense to me, but it took me years to adopt these few methods, and even then, sometimes I forget to use them and quickly regret it.
I will therefore present some ideas and techniques that will serve you in your studies (cuckoo math and physics that hurts!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>