<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The_rest on Think
Love
Share</title>
    <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The_rest on Think
Love
Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Salut, ca va ?</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/salut_ca_va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/salut_ca_va/</guid>
      <description>Salut ! Ca va ?
Ca va ! Et toi ?
Ca va !
 What a useless proloque, right? Riiight?
Well, not exaclty.
What if I told you that this quick chat is in fact useful, and probably one of the most used, daily, worldwide?
Remember of this bad boy? This is him now :)
This is this same kind of exchange used in TCP to establish a connection between a client and a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A question of standards?</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/a_question_of_standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/a_question_of_standards/</guid>
      <description>Hello dear reader,
Today, I would like to talk to you about a deep subject, but in a very superficial way. I would like to talk to you about our society, the groups that are born, live and die in it. Groups, of course, but focused on the individuals who compose them, or who oppose to them.
As usual, I will try to share with you a way of seeing things: mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Une histoire de coquelicot</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/une_histoire_de_coquelicot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/une_histoire_de_coquelicot/</guid>
      <description>Et si, pour varier un peu, on prenait le large ? Et si on laissait la technologie de côté un petit instant, histoire de se divertir ? Et si on lisait un peu ?
Le concept est simple, je reçois un début de texte, d&amp;rsquo;histoire, quelques mots, une idée, et je brode dessus tant bien que mal, en espérant que le rendu final soit sympathique ! =]
Texte proposé Une femme furieuse vêtue d&amp;rsquo;une robe rouge sort du bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning without headache</title>
      <link>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/reasoning_without_headache/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thinkloveshare.com/the_rest/reasoning_without_headache/</guid>
      <description>Today, I propose to take a step back on how to approach problems, research, or even&amp;hellip;. Life in general?
Prologue What I am going to tell you here is common sense to me, but it took me years to adopt these few methods, and even then, sometimes I forget to use them and quickly regret it.
I will therefore present some ideas and techniques that will serve you in your studies (cuckoo math and physics that hurts!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>